android-enjoyed.com 2016-06-01

# Android Enjoyed - Privacy Policy

**Data Collection**

We collect information on our website users in the following ways:

●      When a user registers for the website: The user account registration is optional. The data is stored on our server in United States.

●      When a user places an order in Android Enjoyed Online Store: We collect customer's Physical Contact Address and Internet Contact Address for the sole purpose of processing the order and delivering the goods ordered. PayPal collects your payment information on their website. We do NOT have access to your credit card number or security code. A Android Enjoyed account is automatically registered for you when you shop in our Online Store

●      When a user subscribes to our Online Store Newsletter: Customers may opt-in and opt-out of our Online Store newsletter service. Our newsletter subscription service application may collect customer's demographic data in order to provide suitable content to subscribers. Customers may opt-out of the newsletter at anytime. Instructions on how to opt-out come with every newsletter sent.

●      When a user interacts with a Customer Service representative: We collect information when you interact with Android Enjoyed’s customer service website in order to accurately categorize and respond to customer inquiries and investigate breaches of our terms. 

●      When a user interacts with the website and its applications: We receive information when you interact with and use the Android Enjoyed website and Android Enjoyed Applications.

●      When a user responds to take part in a survey or poll. As a User, you may be invited to participate in polls and surveys from the Android Enjoyed website. Your selection may be random, or it may be based on your non-personally identifiable information. Whether you decide to participate in the poll or survey is completely up to you.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied personal information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Our credit card processor, PayPal – also encrypt your payment details.

**Cookies**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not.

We use cookies to help you remain logged into your account and to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve user experience.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Compliance with Legal Process**

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information, profile information and/or information about your activities as a Android Enjoyed User when required by subpoena or other legal process, or if Android Enjoyed has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (a) investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies; (b) to enforce the User Agreement, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property or personal safety of Android Enjoyed, our Users, employees, or others.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Opt-In/Opt-Out**

Registering as a user and opening a user account is optional. To close an account, please visit our online support centre and submit a ticket. Your user account will be closed and all information removed from our server within 28 days.

To opt-out of our newsletter subscription, please follow the instructions found at the bottom of the newsletter.

**Dispute Resolution**

If visitors or customers have any issues regarding the privacy practice of our website, please email privacy@android-enjoyed.com or write to our Privacy Policy Supervisor at the address below. Our Privacy Policy Supervisor will respond within 10 working days. 

**Privacy Act (AU) California Online Privacy Protection Act (US) Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the Privacy Act (AU) and California Online Privacy Protection Act (US). We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the above mentioned acts, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (US) Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. Our Online Store is directed at people who are at least 18 years old or older.

If you become aware that your child has provided personal information to us without your consent, please contact our Privacy Supervisor at privacy@android-enjoyed.com.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Obligations**

As a User, you have certain obligations to other Users. Some of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of like-minded members such as Android Enjoyed:

●      You must, at all times, abide by the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to third parties (such as trademarks or photographs).

●      You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic, or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of Android Enjoyed and its community of Users.

●      You must not provide to Android Enjoyed and/or other Users information that you believe might be injurious or detrimental to your person or to your professional or social status.

●      You must keep your username and password confidential and not share it with others.

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account at the sole discretion of Android Enjoyed.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us here.
